woof
呜
be careful of AI face swapping
要小心AI 面部互换
hi
hii hi
hey little Rhino Little Robin let's go
嘿 小犀牛 小小罗宾 我们走
嘿 小犀牛 小罗宾 我们走
hey little Rhino Little Robin let's go
play in the park okay I'll be right
小犀牛小罗宾 我们去公园玩吧
在公园里玩玩 好,我马上就来
play in the park okay I'll be right
there Mommy little Rhino and I will be
在公园里玩玩,好吗 我马上到,妈妈小犀牛
妈妈小犀牛和我会在那里
there Mommy little Rhino and I will be
playing in the park don't be too late
妈妈小犀牛和我会在公园玩 别迟到太晚
在公园里玩玩,别迟到
playing in the park don't be too late
I'm here
我在这里
little Rhino where are you
小犀牛,你在哪里?
I'm here
小犀牛,你在哪里? 我在这里
我在这里
I'm here
hi little rabbit huh
我在这里 嗨小兔子,是吧?
小兔子,哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
hi little rabbit huh
you're not little rhino
你不是小犀牛
I am little Rhino who are
你不是小犀牛 我是小犀牛
can be whoever I want I can even become
成为我想要成为的任何人 甚至可以成为
you
我想成为谁就成为谁 我甚至可以成为你
come with me
跟我来
oh little Rhino hi Miss Rabbit is little
跟我来哦 小犀牛 嗨 兔子小姐是小
哦 小犀牛 嗨 兔子小姐是小
oh little Rhino hi Miss Rabbit is little
rabbit home didn't you ask her on the
哦 小犀牛 嗨 兔子小姐是小兔子家 你没有问过她吗?
兔子回家 你没有问过她吗?
rabbit home didn't you ask her on the
video call to go outside and play huh I
兔子家,你不是在视频电话里 让她出去玩吗?
视频电话到外面玩
video call to go outside and play huh I
didn't even call her
视频电话到外面玩游戏 我甚至都没打给她
what
什么什么是
oh sheriff Labrador someone on the video
拉布拉多警长在录像里
拉布拉多警长 有人在视频里
oh sheriff Labrador someone on the video
called disguised as little Rhino tricked
拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 视频里有人 伪装成小犀牛的诡计
伪装成小犀牛的诡计
called disguised as little Rhino tricked
my daughter into going to the park
伪装成小犀牛 骗我女儿去公园
我女儿去公园
my daughter into going to the park
a bad person must have taken her hmm
我女儿去公园 一定是坏人把她带走了
一定是坏人把她带走了
a bad person must have taken her hmm
looks like another case of AI face
一个坏人一定把她带走了 看起来像是另一例AI脸
看起来像是另一例人工智能脸部
looks like another case of AI face
swapping fraud little rabbit's in Danger
仿佛另一例AI 面临欺诈骗骗小兔子在危险中
诈骗诈骗小兔子在危险中
swapping fraud little rabbit's in Danger
let's go to the park
诈骗诈骗小兔子在危险中,我们去公园吧
let's split up here okay
我们分开吧,好吗?
excuse me have you seen little rabbit
对不起,你见过小兔子吗?
around
周围
thank you
谢谢大家
感谢您,感谢您
thank you
oh no the police is here hello I want to
谅谅 瓳 ⊿Τ牡诡ㄓ 顿 и稱
哦,没有警察来了,你好,我想打招呼
oh no the police is here hello I want to
go home
哦,没有警察在这里 你好,我想回家
回家回家回家
go home
well I don't say anything
回家好,我什么也不说
我什么也不说
well I don't say anything
little rabbit
小小兔子
little rabbit where are you you can't
小兔子,你在哪里 你不能在哪里
see me you can't see me
小兔子你在哪里 你看不见我 你看不见我
看见我,你看不见我
see me you can't see me
a rabbit here
看见我,你不能在这里看到兔子
一只兔子在这里
a rabbit here
hey
嘿
little rabbit
小小兔子
Sheriff Labrador
小兔子警长拉布拉多
hit this
按下这个
where did she go
她去哪里了? 去哪里了?
enter the supermarket let's go
她从哪儿进超市的? 走吧
okay
还好
how do we find her Dobby guard the door
我们怎么找到她的多比守门?
appeal use your equipment to find her
我们怎么找到她的多比 保护门警 使用你的设备找到她
使用您的设备来寻找她
appeal use your equipment to find her
Daddy it's time to use my new invention
利用你的设备来寻找她的爸爸 是时候利用我的新发明了
爸爸 是时候用我的新发明了
Daddy it's time to use my new invention
oh in position good now wait for Intel
等待英特尔
to show up oh
等待英特尔出现
露露出来哦
to show up oh
okay
还好
another one
彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此彼此
stop right there
站在那里别动
huh why are there two Dobies zoom in the
为什么有两张Dobies 缩放在
screen
为什么屏幕上有两个多比斯放大?
foreign
外国
with AI face swapping let's go
和AI互换面孔,我们走吧
where did she go
她去哪里了? 去哪里了?
watch me
她去哪里看我了? 她去哪儿了?
看着我
watch me
thank you
感谢您,感谢您
I can't see anything
我什么都看不见
you can't run away
你跑不掉的,你跑不掉的
you're coming with us
跟我们一起走
oh Mission failed the police are smarter
你跟我们一起去哦任务失败了 警察更聪明
任务失败了,警察更聪明
oh Mission failed the police are smarter
than I thought
任务失败了 警察比我想的聪明
比我想象的
than I thought
now it's your turn yes
现在轮到你了,是的,是的
Sheriff Labradors safety dock
拉布拉多警长安全码头
kids on video calls bad people can use
坏人可以使用
AI to trick you by making faces of your
坏人可以使用人工智能欺骗你,
AI来欺骗你 通过制造你的面孔
AI to trick you by making faces of your
friends and family members
AI 来欺骗你 做朋友和家人的面孔
和家庭成员的朋友和家庭成员的权利
friends and family members
it's good to have a secret code with our
朋友和家人的朋友 很高兴能和我们有秘密的密码
和我们有一个秘密密码是件好事
it's good to have a secret code with our
family and friends so that we can
和我们的家人和朋友有秘密密码 这样我们就可以
家属和朋友,以便我们能够
family and friends so that we can
recognize each other please be careful
家人和朋友,这样我们才能互相认识 一定要小心一点
互相认识时,请小心认识对方
recognize each other please be careful
of your calls
认得对方 请小心你们的电话
与您的调用
of your calls
foreign
外国
本字幕由AI大模型生成